[
    {
        "Question": "When does the geometric series test converge",
        "QuestionImage": "null",
        "Answer1": "(-1, 1)",
        "Answer2": "(0, 1)",
        "Answer3": "(-1, 0)",
        "Answer4": "None of the above",
        "CorrectAnswer": 1,
    },
    {
        "Question": "When does the p-series test converge",
        "QuestionImage": "null",
        "Answer1": "(-1, 1)",
        "Answer2": "(0, 1)",
        "Answer3": "(-1, 0)",
        "Answer4": "None of the above",
        "CorrectAnswer": 4,
    },
    {
        "Question": "By what test can the series convergence be determined?",
        "QuestionImage": "RatioQuestion",
        "Answer1": "Root",
        "Answer2": "Limit Comparison",
        "Answer3": "Comparison",
        "Answer4": "Ratio",
        "CorrectAnswer": 4,
    },
    {
        "Question": "Does the Series Diverge or Converge? By which test?",
        "QuestionImage": "RootQuestion",
        "Answer1": "Converge by Root Test",
        "Answer2": "Diverge by Root Test",
        "Answer3": "Converge by Alternating Series Test",
        "Answer4": "Diverge by Alternating Series Test",
        "CorrectAnswer": 2,
    },
    {
        "Question": "Does the Series Diverge or Converge? By which test?",
        "QuestionImage": "SeriesQuestion1",
        "Answer1": "Converge by Root Test",
        "Answer2": "Diverge by Root Test",
        "Answer3": "Converge by Geometric Series Test",
        "Answer4": "Diverge by Geometric Series Test",
        "CorrectAnswer": 3,
    },
    {
        "Question": "Select the correct answer",
        "QuestionImage": "null",
        "Answer1": "Less than diverging diverges",
        "Answer2": "Less than diverging converges",
        "Answer3": "Greater than diverging diverges",
        "Answer4": "Greater than diverging converges",
        "CorrectAnswer": 3,
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which series is correct to compare to the original using a comparison test?",
        "QuestionImage": "SeriesQuestion2",
        "Answer1": "n+1",
        "Answer2": "1/n",
        "Answer3": "1/(n+1)",
        "Answer4": "None of the above",
        "CorrectAnswer": 2,
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the sum of a geometric series?",
        "QuestionImage": "null",
        "Answer1": "a/(1-r)",
        "Answer2": "a/(1+r)",
        "Answer3": "(a-1)/r",
        "Answer4": "r/(1-a)",
        "CorrectAnswer": 1,
    },
    {
        "Question": "What does the divergence test state?",
        "QuestionImage": "null",
        "Answer1": "If the limit as n aproches infinity of a series exists and does not equal 0 the series converges.",
        "Answer2": "If the limit as n aproches 0 of a series exists and does not equal 0 the series diverges.",
        "Answer3": "If the limit as n aproches infinity of a series equals 0 than the series diverges.",
        "Answer4": "If the limit as n aproches infinity of a series exists and does not equal 0 the series diverges.",
        "CorrectAnswer": 4,
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the series of Cos(x)?",
        "QuestionImage": "null",
        "Answer1": "x - x^3/3! + x^5/5! - ...",
        "Answer2": "1 + x + x^2/2! + x^3/3! + ...",
        "Answer3": "1 - x + x^2/2! - x^3/3! + ...",
        "Answer4": "1 - x^2/2! + x^4/4! - ...",
        "CorrectAnswer": 4,
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the first term represented by the sum of a series 5/(1+x^2)?",
        "QuestionImage": "null",
        "Answer1": "x^2",
        "Answer2": "-x^2",
        "Answer3": "5",
        "Answer4": "1",
        "CorrectAnswer": 3,
    },
    {
        "Question": "What test could be used on the series?",
        "QuestionImage": "SeriesQuestion3",
        "Answer1": "P-Series Test",
        "Answer2": "Geometric Series Test",
        "Answer3": "Ratio Test",
        "Answer4": "Integral Test",
        "CorrectAnswer": 4,
    },
    {
        "Question": "What test could be used on the series?",
        "QuestionImage": "SeriesQuestion4",
        "Answer1": "P-Series Test",
        "Answer2": "Alternating Series Test",
        "Answer3": "Ratio Test",
        "Answer4": "Geometric Series Test",
        "CorrectAnswer": 2,
    },
]
